snapeda.com 2019-07-31

# Privacy Policy | SnapEDA

Your privacy is very important to us. Accordingly, we have developed this Policy in order for you to understand how we collect, use, communicate, disclose and make use of personal information. The following outlines our privacy policy. 

  * Before or at the time of collecting personal information, we will identify the purposes for which information is being collected. 
  * We will collect and use personal information solely with the objective of fulfilling those purposes specified by us and for other compatible purposes, unless we obtain the consent of the individual concerned or as required by law. 
  * We will only retain personal information as long as necessary for the fulfillment of those purposes. 
  * We will collect personal information by lawful and fair means and, where appropriate, with the knowledge or consent of the individual concerned. 
  * Personal data should be relevant to the purposes for which it is to be used, and, to the extent necessary for those purposes, should be accurate, complete, and up-to-date. 
  * We will protect personal information by reasonable security safeguards against loss or theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification. 
  * We will make readily available to customers, information about our policies and practices relating to the management of personal information. 
  * When visitors come to SnapEDA, third parties (such as AdRoll) may place cookies on their browsers for targeted advertising purposes. 
  * We may collect the following information: location, device and browser information for targeted advertising purposes. 
  * We may share aggregate information (without individually identifying information) with third parties. 
  * To keep SnapEDA free, we work with advertisers. We provide them with reports about the kinds of people seeing their ads, but we don't share personal information that identifies you. 
  * We may provide general demographic information to advertisers (for example, that an ad was seen by a woman between the ages of 25 and 34 who lives in San Francisco and uses Altium) to help them better understand their audience. 
  * To quantify the performance of their ads, we may disclose which keywords were used to find an ad, or anonymously attribute the view of an ad with a purchase. 
  * To opt-out of targeted advertising, please [notify us](mailto:info@snapeda.com)
  * This Privacy Policy is intended to meet our duties of transparency under the "General Data Protection Regulation" or "GDPR"." 

We are committed to conducting our business in accordance with these principles in order to ensure that the confidentiality of personal information is protected and maintained.
